<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sara &#43; Brian on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sara &#43; Brian on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>La fiesta</title>
      <link>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page1/</guid>
      <description>We are getting married!
We love you
Come celebrate with us :)
When Saturday, October 30th, 2021
Ceremony: 2:30pm
Aperitivo: 3:00pm
Dinner: 4:30pm
Where La Selva Giardino del Belvedere
Montegonzi, Cavriglia, Tuscany, Italy
Learn more about this beautiful place here and here!
Attire Cocktail
More fun  Informal grill at the Villa: Friday, October 29th, 2021 at 5pm Masquerade Pizza Party at the Villa: Sunday, October 31st, 2021 at noon (It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preguntas</title>
      <link>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page2/</guid>
      <description>How do we get there?  See here for directions and transportation options to Montevarchi, the nearest town to the villa See here for driving directions to the villa - we recommend you print these out if you’re driving! See here for a video of the drive from A1 VALDARNO Exit See here for a geolocation of the villa in Google Maps IMPORTANT: your phone signal may not be strong in the area around the villa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Que mas</title>
      <link>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcfujiy.github.io/sarabrian-wedding/page3/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Tuscany We hope you’ll get to experience Tuscany (and Italy) while you’re here - whether together with us or on your own. In the region, we’ve enjoyed exploring small towns, visiting markets and castles, and of course eating our way across the countryside.
There are lots of places to visit nearby; including 7 UNESCO World Heritage Sites within 60 to 90 minutes by car or train. Tuscany is the region with the largest number of UNESCO World Heritage Properties in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>